Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - I-L
        - Jackson, Millie - Live and uncensored (Disc two), 1979; SR-26735; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26734. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-2-6725; A-side Matrix # SP-2-6725-CS-K
        - Jackson, Millie - Lovers and girlfriends, 1982; SR-26736; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # PRO 177; A-side Matrix # PRO-177-AS-BLEEPED
        - Jackson, Millie - Free and in love, 1976; SR-26737; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # SEW 032; A-side Matrix # 007 DMD-6075 A-1
          Southbound
        - Jackson, Millie - I had to say it, 1980; SR-26738; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-1-6730; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6730 AS-DI-PLU
        - Jackson, Millie - Lovingly yours, 1976; SR-26739; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-1-6712; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6712 AS-CP2
        - Jackson, Millie - Get it out'cha system, 1978; SR-26740; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-1-6719; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6719-AS-DI-GD
        - Jackson, Rebbie - Reaction, 1986; SR-26741; Jackson, Rebbie (Box 41)
          Catalog # C 40364; A-side Matrix # PAL 40364-1A
          Columbia
        - Jackson Sisters - I believe in miracles, 1973; SR-26742; Jackson Sisters (Box 41)
          Catalog # TLR1001; A-side Matrix # TLR-1001A
          Tiger Lily Records
        - Jacksons - Goin' places, 1977; SR-26743; Jacksons (Box 41)
          Catalog # JE 34835; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AL-34835-2A
        - Jacksons - Working day and night, 1982; SR-26744; Jacksons (Box 41)
          Catalog # AS 1387; A-side Matrix # XSS 168922 1B
        - Jacksons - 2300 Jackson Street, 1989; SR-26745; Jacksons (Box 41)
          Catalog # E 40911; A-side Matrix # PAL-40911-1A
        - Jacksons - 2300 Jackson Street, 1989; SR-26746; Jacksons (Box 41)
        - Jacksons - Triumph, 1980; SR-26747; Jacksons (Box 41)
          Catalog # FE 36424; A-side Matrix # PAL-36424-1AM
        - Jagged Edge - Jagged little thrill (Disc one), 2001; SR-26748; Jagged Edge (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26749. Double album.
          Catalog # COL 503344 1; A-side Matrix # 5033441000 1A1
          Netherlands
        - Jagged Edge - Jagged little thrill (Disc two), 2001; SR-26749; Jagged Edge (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26748. Double album.
          Catalog # COL 503344 1; A-side Matrix # 5033441000 1C1
        - Jam - The gift, 1982; SR-26750; Jam (Box 41)
          Catalog # PD-1-6349; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6349-AS-HRM
        - Jamaica Boys - The Jamaica Boys, 1987; SR-26751; Jamaica Boys (Box 41)
          Catalog # 1-25615; A-side Matrix # 1-25615-A-DMM-SR1 SP 1-1
        - Jambalasie - Chains on the mind, 1975; SR-26752; Jambalasie; Scipio Sargeant (Box 41)
          Catalog # GS 7794; A-side Matrix # GS-7794-A
          Straker's Records
        - James, Bob - Lucky seven, 1979; SR-26753; James, Bob (Box 41)
          Catalog # JC 36056; A-side Matrix # P AL 36056-2A
        - James, Etta - Come a little closer, 1974; SR-26754; James, Etta (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26755. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CH 60029; A-side Matrix # T | CH 60029-A-1 TML
          Chess
        - James, Etta - Come a little closer, 1974; SR-26755; James, Etta (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26754. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CH 60029; A-side Matrix # CH 60029-A
        - James, Janet - Love to be the one, 1980; SR-26756; James, Janet (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26757. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NW-913; A-side Matrix # NW-913-AP20
          NelWin Records
        - James, Janet - Love to be the one, 1980; SR-26757; James, Janet (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26756. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NW-913; A-side Matrix # NR-101-A
        - James, Bob - Sign of the times, 1981; SR-26758; James, Bob (Box 41)
          Catalog # FC 37495; A-side Matrix # AL 37495-1AB
        - James, Jimmy - You don't stand a chance if you can't dance, 1975; SR-26759; James, Jimmy; Jimmy James And The Vagabonds (Box 41)
          Catalog # PYE 12111; A-side Matrix # PYE-12111-AS-1A
          Pye Records
        - James, Rick - Bustin' out of L seven, 1979; SR-26760; James, Rick (Box 41)
          Catalog # G7-984R1; A-side Matrix # G7-984R1-A-13E PBR
          Gordy
        - James, Rick - Cold blooded, 1983; SR-26761; James, Rick (Box 41)
          Catalog # 6043GL; A-side Matrix # 6043-GL-15B-A ZKA#13 APRN
        - James, Rick - Street songs, 1981; SR-26762; James, Rick (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26763. Different discs.
          Catalog # G8-1002M1; A-side Matrix # G8-I002MI-A-15B 3X3 #13
        - James, Rick - Super freak, 1981; SR-26763; James, Rick (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26762. Different discs.
          Catalog # PR-83; A-side Matrix # PR-83-A-66308-D-15A
        - James, Rick - Wonderful, 1988; SR-26764; James, Rick (Box 42)
          Catalog # 1-25659; A-side Matrix # 1-25659-A-SR4
          Reprise Records
        - James, Rick - Blow, 1982; SR-26765; James, Rick (Box 42)
          Catalog # 6023GL; A-side Matrix # 6023 GLA15D ZNN S-13 BNI
        - James, Rick - Give it to me baby, 1981; SR-26766; James, Rick (Box 42)
          Catalog # PR-81; A-side Matrix # PR81-A SIDE 66313-D-15B JWB #13
        - Jamiroquai - Alright (Disc one), 1997; SR-26767; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26768. Double album.
          Catalog # XPR 3104; A-side Matrix # 31 3104 20 1A1
          Sony Soho Square
        - Jamiroquai - Alright (Disc two), 1997; SR-26768; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26767. Double album.
          Catalog # XPR 3104; A-side Matrix # 32 3104 20 1C1
        - Jamiroquai - Cosmic girl, 1996; SR-26769; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          Catalog # XPR 3087; A-side Matrix # 31 3087 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - Emergency on planet Earth (Disc one), 1993; SR-26770; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          Double album. Missing disc two.
          Catalog # 474069 1; A-side Matrix # 01 474069 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - Virtual insanity, 1996; SR-26771; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          Catalog # 31 3077 20 1; A-side Matrix # 31 3077 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - Alright, 1997; SR-26772; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          Catalog # XPR3113; A-side Matrix # 31 3113 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - Half the man, 1994; SR-26773; Jamiroquai (Box 42)
          Catalog # 661003 6; A-side Matrix # 01 661003 20 1A1
        - Jammers - The Jammers, 1982; SR-26774; Jammers (Box 42)
          Catalog # SA 8556; A-side Matrix # SA-8557-A
        - Jarreau, Al - Look to the rainbow (Disc one), 1977; SR-26775; Jarreau, Al (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26776. Double album.
          Catalog # 2BZ 3052; A-side Matrix # 2BZ-1-3053 LW-2
        - Jarreau, Al - Look to the rainbow (Disc two), 1977; SR-26776; Jarreau, Al (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26775. Double album.
          Catalog # 2BZ 3052; A-side Matrix # 2BZ-3-3053 LW-1
        - Jarreau, Al - All fly home, 1978; SR-26777; Jarreau, Al (Box 42)
          Catalog # BSK 3229; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3229-LW1
        - Jarrett, Keith - Shades, 1976; SR-26778; Jarrett, Keith (Box 42)
          Catalog # AS-9322; A-side Matrix # AS-9322-A
          Impulse!
        - Jasp 182 - Ricochet; If the sun never rises again, 1997; SR-26779; Jasp 182 (Box 42)
          Catalog # LBS001-12; A-side Matrix # SASP-182-A
          Insomniac
        - Jayo Felony - Whatcha gonna do, 1998; SR-26780; Jayo Felony (Box 42)
          Catalog # BAS 41062; A-side Matrix # XSS-41062A-1B
          Yab Yum Records
        - Jay Peel - Gimme some; reflections, 1983; SR-26783; Jay Peel (Box 42)
          Catalog # 815 626-1; A-side Matrix # 816 626-1S1 320
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Jaye, Miles - Miles, 1987; SR-26784; Jaye, Miles (Box 42)
          Catalog # 90615-1; A-side Matrix # ST-1L-876423-A
        - Jazaq - Come on party people (lets ge down), 1985; SR-26785; Jazaq; Crazy Eddie (Box 42)
          Catalog # EN-6037; A-side Matrix # EN6037-A
          Enjoy Records
        - Jazzi P - Feel the rhythm, 1990; SR-26786; Jazzi P (Box 42)
          Catalog # USAT 691; A-side Matrix # USAT 691 A-1U-1-1
        - Jazzy Jeff - Fire, 1985; SR-26787; Jazzy Jeff (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26788. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JDI-9427; A-side Matrix # JD-I-9427-SA-ESI
          Jive
        - Jazzy Jeff - Fire, 1985; SR-26788; Jazzy Jeff (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26787. 2 copies.
        - J.B.'s Internationals - Jam II disco fever, 1978; SR-26789; J.B.'s Internationals (Box 42)
          Catalog # PD-1-6153; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6153-AS-AD
        - J.B.'s - Funky good times: the anthology volume 2 (Disc one), 1995; SR-26790; J.B.'s (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26791. Double album.
          Catalog # SVLP 168; A-side Matrix # 08 42782 201A1 SVLP 168
        - J.B.'s - Funky good times: the anthology volume 2 (Disc two), 1995; SR-26791; J.B.'s (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26790. Double album.
          Catalog # SVLP 168; A-side Matrix # 08 42782 201C1 SVLP 168
        - J.B.'s - Rock groove machine; Rock, 1979; SR-26792; J.B.'s (Box 42)
          Catalog # TKD-150; A-side Matrix # TKD-150-A
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - J.B.'s - Groove machine, 1979; SR-26793; J.B.'s (Box 42)
          Catalog # DR-111; A-side Matrix # DR-111-A-AM
          Drive
        - Jean, Wyclef - The carnival (Disc one), 1997; SR-26794; Jean, Wyclef; Refugee Allstars (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26795. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67974; A-side Matrix # AL-67185-1B
        - Jean, Wyclef - The carnival (Disc two), 1997; SR-26795; Jean, Wyclef; Refugee Allstars (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26794. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67974; A-side Matrix # AL-67186-1B
        - Jean, Wyclef - Gone till November, 1997; SR-26796; Jean, Wyclef (Box 42)
          Catalog # 44 778753; A-side Matrix # XSS 78753A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Jefferson, Morris - Spank your blank blank, 1978; SR-26797; Jefferson, Morris (Box 42)
          Catalog # RRLP 9003 DJ; A-side Matrix # RRLP 9003 AS-4-CP
          Parachute Records
        - Jeffreys, Garland - One-Eyed Jack, 1978; SR-26798; Jeffreys, Garland (Box 42)
          Catalog # SP-4681; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 5099-T2
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Jellybean - Just visiting this planet, 1987; SR-26799; Jellybean (Box 42)
          Catalog # BVF 41569; A-side Matrix # BVF 41569 AS DMM-X STERLING
          Chrysalis
        - Jesús Acosta & The Professionals - You are there!, 1975; SR-26800; Jesús Acosta & The Professionals (Box 42)
          Catalog # LP 7406; A-side Matrix # SLP 7406-A
          CES
          Belize City, Belize
        - Jesus From Ibiza - Gone, 2003; SR-26801; Jesus From Ibiza (Box 42)
          Catalog # 82876 55136 1; A-side Matrix # B38+289-01 A1
          Low Spirit Recordings
          Berlin, Germany
        - Jessie G. - That's hot, 1981; SR-26802; Jessie G. (Box 42)
          Catalog # ETC 52; A-side Matrix # NG-1-A
          Nugget Records
          Cherry Hill, New Jersey
        - Jets - Magic, 1980; SR-26803; Jets (Box 42)
          Catalog # MCA-42085; A-side Matrix # MCA-7190-FDS-1
        - Jets - The Jets, 1985; SR-26804; Jets (Box 42)
          Catalog # MCA-5667; A-side Matrix # MCA-4791-FDS-2
        - Jiani, Carol - Hit 'n run lover; All the people of the world, 1981; SR-26805; Jiani, Carol (Box 42)
          Catalog # W-12044; A-side Matrix # W-12044-A
          Matra
          Saint-Laurent, Quebec, Canada
        - Jigsaw - Jigsaw, 1977; SR-26806; Jigsaw (Box 42)
          Catalog # T-545; A-side Matrix # M-545-AS P-2
          20th Century Records
        - Jimmy Castor Brunch - The Jimmy Castor Brunch, 1979; SR-26807; Jimmy Castor Brunch (Box 42)
          Catalog # SD 5215; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-794321
          Cotillion
        - J.J. Fad - Supersonic - the album, 1988; SR-26808; J.J. Fad (Box 42)
          Catalog # 90959-1; A-side Matrix # ST-RU-886967-A
          Ruthless Records
        - Unknown artist - JMP 3, 2000; SR-26809; Unknown artist (Box 42)
          Catalog # PM 104; A-side Matrix # 0005Y36-A
          Not on label
          Fort Worth, Texas
        - JNX - Givin' me luv; Little bit higher, 1995; SR-26810; JNX (Box 42)
          Catalog # SM-9024-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9024-0-A
          Sm:)e House Works
        - JNX - Givin' me luv; Little bit higher, 1995; SR-26811; JNX (Box 42)
        - JoBoxers - Boxerbeat, 1983; SR-26812; JoBoxers (Box 42)
          Catalog # BOXT 1; A-side Matrix # BOXT 1 A-2U-1-1
          RCA
        - J. Jocko - That's the song, 1975; SR-26813; J. Jocko (Box 42)
          Catalog # KSBS 2604; A-side Matrix # KSBS-2604 A
          Kama Sutra
        - Jodeci - The show the after party the hotel (Disc one), 1995; SR-26814; Jodeci (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26815. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA 11258; A-side Matrix # MCA 11258 A-1-1-1
        - Jodeci - The show the after party the hotel (Disc two), 1995; SR-26815; Jodeci (Box 42)
          In same jacket as # SR-26814. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA 11258; A-side Matrix # MCA 11258 C-1-1-1
        - Joeski Love - Joe cool, 1990; SR-26816; Joeski Love (Box 42)
          Catalog # C 45474; A-side Matrix # AL-45474 1A
        - John, Elton - Get up and dance, 1977; SR-26817; John, Elton (Box 42)
          Catalog # MCA2-11004; A-side Matrix # MCA 1173 W-2
        - John, Robert - Back on the street, 1980; SR-26818; John, Robert (Box 42)
          Catalog # SW-17027; A-side Matrix # SW-1-17027Z G4
          EMI America
        - Jonny Guitar Watson - Love Jones, 1980; SR-26819; Jonny Guitar Watson (Box 42)
          Catalog # DJM-31; A-side Matrix # DJM-31 PRC-R A-2
          DJM Records
        - Johnson, Beverly - Don't lose the feeling, 1979; SR-26820; Johnson, Beverly (Box 43)
          Catalog # BDS 5726; A-side Matrix # BDS 5726 SA CT2
        - Johnson, Coby - Walking saw, 1997; SR-26821; Johnson, Coby; Lindsey, Patrick (Box 43)
          Catalog # School 04; A-side Matrix # SCH00Z 04 A
          School Records
          Germany
        - Johnson, General - General Johnson, 1976; SR-26822; Johnson, General (Box 43)
          Catalog # AL 4082; A-side Matrix # AL 4082-SA
        - Johnson, Jesse - Jesse Johnson's Revue, 1985; SR-26823; Johnson, Jesse; Jesse Johnson's Revue (Box 43)
          Catalog # SP-6-5024; A-side Matrix # SP06-5024-A ESI
        - Johnson, Jesse - Shockadelica, 1986; SR-26824; Johnson, Jesse (Box 43)
          Catalog # SP-5122; A-side Matrix # SPO 5122-A ESI
        - Johnson, Linton Kwesi - Dread beat an' blood, 1981; SR-26825; Johnson, Linton Kwesi (Box 43)
          Catalog # 39434; A-side Matrix # 39434A
          Heartbeat Records
          Cambridge, Massachusetts
        - Johnson, Dr. Perri - Kick it out, 1984; SR-26826; Johnson, Dr. Perri (Box 43)
          Catalog # PRO-7053; A-side Matrix # PRO-7053-A
          Profile Records
        - Johnson, Kevin - Ocean drive E.P., 2000; SR-26827; Johnson, Kevin (Box 43)
          Catalog # DNH-073; A-side Matrix # DNH073-A
          DNH Records
          Toronto, Canada
        - Joli, France - Tonight, 1980; SR-26828; Joli, France (Box 43)
          Catalog # PRL 12179; A-side Matrix # P RL-12179 AS-1B
        - Joli, France - Now, 1982; SR-26829; Joli, France (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26830. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRL 14103; A-side Matrix # PRL-14103-AS
        - Joli, France - Now, 1982; SR-26830; Joli, France (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26829. Different discs.
        - Joli, France - Witch of love, 1985; SR-26831; Joli, France (Box 43)
          Catalog # FE 39934; A-side Matrix # PAL-39934-1B
        - Jon Spencer Blues Explosion - Talk about the blues, 1998; SR-26832; Jon Spencer Blues Explosion (Box 43)
          Catalog # OLE 327-1; A-side Matrix # OLE-327-1-A
          Matador
        - Jumbo - Turn on to love, 1976; SR-26833; Jumbo (Box 43)
          Catalog # PYE 12142; A-side Matrix # PYE-12142-A
        - Jones, Booker T. - The best of you, 1980; SR-26834; Jones, Booker T. (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26835. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-4798; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO4798A-T2
        - Jones, Booker T. - The best of you, 1980; SR-26835; Jones, Booker T. (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26834. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-4798; A-side Matrix # A&M 04798A-T1
        - Jones, Busta - (You) keep on making me hot, 1979; SR-26836; Jones, Busta (Box 43)
          Catalog # PRO 118; A-side Matrix # PRO-118-79NP-4366-S-CPI
        - Jones Girls - You gonna make me love somebody else, 1979; SR-26837; Jones Girls (Box 43)
          Catalog # 2Z8 3682; A-side Matrix # PIR AA-2Z8-3682-3
          Philadelphia International Rceords
        - Jones, Glenn - Take it from me, 1986; SR-26838; Jones, Glenn (Box 43)
          Catalog # AFL1-5807; A-side Matrix # AFL-1- 5807-A-1
        - Jones, Grace - Muse, 1979; SR-26839; Jones, Grace (Box 43)
          Catalog # ILPS 9538; A-side Matrix # ILPS-1-9538-LW2
        - Jones, Grace - Living my life, 1982; SR-26840; Jones, Grace (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26841. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 90018-1; A-side Matrix # STIL 825055 C 0-1 SM2-1
        - Jones, Grace - Living my life, 1982; SR-26841; Jones, Grace (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26840. 2 copies.
        - Jones, Jill - Jill Jones, 1987; SR-26842; Jones, Jill (Box 43)
          Catalog # 1-25575; A-side Matrix # 1-25575-A-SR4
          Paisley Park
        - Jones, Jill - G-spot (the 12" remix), 1987; SR-26843; Jones, Jill (Box 43)
          Catalog # 0-20756; A-side Matrix # 0-20756-ASH1 B-28915-SH1 △18014
        - Jones, Jimmy "Handyman" - Handyman's back in town (part II), 1976; SR-26844; Jones, Jimmy "Handyman"; Jones Family (Box 43)
          Catalog # SR 1000-1; A-side Matrix # 1000-A
          Jen-Jillus Records
        - Jones, Karen - Come together, 1990; SR-26845; Jones, Karen (Box 43)
          Catalog # FTM 31664; A-side Matrix # FTM 31664 A
          London Street
          Italy
        - Jones, Quincy - $ (Music from the original motion picture sound track), 1972; SR-26846; Jones, Quincy (Box 43)
          Catalog # MS 2051; A-side Matrix # T1 MS-2051 31356-1-1
        - Jones, Quincy - The dude, 1981; SR-26847; Jones, Quincy (Box 43)
          Catalog # SP-17147; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO17147A-S1
        - Jones, Tamiko - Cloudy, 1977; SR-26848; Jones, Tamiko (Box 43)
          Catalog # ATL-715; A-side Matrix # XSY-148 676-1B ATL-715-A
          Atlantis Records II
        - Jonzun, Michael - Money isn't everything, 1986; SR-26849; Jonzun, Michael (Box 43)
          Catalog # SP-5111; A-side Matrix # SPO-5111-A
        - Jordan, Ronny - So what!, 1992; SR-26850; Jordan, Ronny (Box 43)
          Catalog # 12 ANN 14; A-side Matrix # DFI 92 112 ANN 14 A
          Antilles
        - Joseph, David - You can't hide, 1983; SR-26851; Joseph, David (Box 43)
          Catalog # PRO 7804; A-side Matrix # PRO-7804-A
        - Jovanotti - Jovanotti for president, 1988; SR-26852; Jovanotti (Box 43)
          Catalog # IBZ 461200 1; A-side Matrix # IBZ 461200-1 A
          Ibiza Records
          Milan, Italy
        - J.T. Connection - Bernadette; Reach out I'll be there, 1979; SR-26853; J.T. Connection; Tufano, Dennis (Box 43)
          Catalog # FLY-13925; A-side Matrix # MCA-1850
          Butterfly Rceords
        - Judas Priest - Hell bent for leather, 1978; SR-26854; Judas Priest (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26855. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JC 35706; A-side Matrix # PAL 35706-1D
        - Judas Priest - Hell bent for leather, 1978; SR-26855; Judas Priest (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26854. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JC 35706; A-side Matrix # P AL 35706-1A
        - Jungle Brothers - Done by the forces of nature, 1989; SR-26856; Jungle Brothers (Box 43)
          Catalog # 1-26072; A-side Matrix # 1-26072-A SR1
        - Junie - Bread alone, 1980; SR-26857; Junie; Morrison, Junie (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26858. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NJC 36585; A-side Matrix # D AL 36585-1A
        - Junie - Bread alone, 1980; SR-26858; Junie; Morrison, Junie (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26857. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NJC 36585; A-side Matrix # D AL 36585-1B
        - JV - What we have here, 1996; SR-26859; JV; Buckwhead (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26860. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TH-2228-1; A-side Matrix # S-33000 TH-2228-A
          Thump Records
          Walnut, California
        - JV - What we have here, 1996; SR-26860; JV; Buckwhead (Box 43)
          In same jacket as # SR-26859. 2 copies.
        - K-Life - P@#$yda bomb !, 1999; SR-24268; K-Life (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24269. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FB-III; A-side Matrix # FB-III-A
          Fully Blown Records
        - K-Life - P@#$yda bomb !, 1999; SR-24269; K-Life (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24268. 2 copies.
        - Kabala - La Kabala, 1990; SR-24270; Kabala (Box 44)
          Catalog # DS-203; A-side Matrix # HIJACKERS
          Discos Sonrisa
        - Kader - Arabfunk, 1988; SR-24271; Kader (Box 44)
          Catalog # DEMS 010; A-side Matrix # DEM AX-006-A
          Day Eight Music
        - Kaine - Wisdom rock, 1985; SR-24272; Kaine (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24273. 2 copies.
          Catalog # KA 1827; A-side Matrix # KA-1827-A
          K-Star Records
        - Kaine - Wisdom rock, 1985; SR-24273; Kaine (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24272. 2 copies.
        - Kaleidoscope - Space is the place; Tour de force, 1996; SR-24274; Kaleidoscope (Box 44)
          Catalog # IGN005; A-side Matrix # IGN 005 A21
          Ignition Musik
        - Kalyan - All the way, 1980; SR-24275; Kalyan (Box 44)
          Catalog # AFL1-3514; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3514-A-1
        - Kane Gang - Small town creed, 1984; SR-24276; Kane Gang (Box 44)
          Catalog # SKX11; A-side Matrix # SKX 11 A
          Kitchenware Records
          Newcastle-Upon-Tyne, United Kingdom
        - Kane, Madleen - Cheri, 1979; SR-24277; Kane, Madleen (Box 44)
          Catalog # BSK 3315; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3315-LW1
          Warner Bros Records
        - Kano - Now baby now; Super extra sexy sign, 1980; SR-24278; Kano (Box 44)
          Catalog # EMDS-6516; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6516-NOW BABY NOW
          Emergency Records
        - Kantata - Asiko; Duke, 1984; SR-24279; Kantata (Box 44)
          Catalog # OVALT 30/12; A-side Matrix # OVALT-30/12-A3
          Oval
        - Kante, Mory - Akwaba beach, 1987; SR-24280; Kante, Mory (Box 44)
          Catalog # 833 119-1; A-side Matrix # 833 119-1 S1
          Barclay
          Paris, France
        - Kaos - Some girls, 1994; SR-24281; Kaos (Box 44)
          Catalog # 374631335-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 1335-1-A
        - Karavan - The funk is gonna get you yet; Never alone, 1983; SR-24282; Karavan (Box 44)
          Catalog # AS 1627; A-side Matrix # XSM-170837-1A
        - Karma - For everybody, 1977; SR-24283; Karma (Box 44)
          Catalog # SP-723; A-side Matrix # SP-745-T1
          Horizon
        - Kartoon Krew - Inspector gadget, 1985; SR-24284; Kartoon Krew (Box 44)
          Catalog # PRO-7087; A-side Matrix # PRO-7087-A
          Profile
        - Kassav' - Kassav', 1985; SR-24285; Kassav' (Box 44)
          Catalog # GD 027; A-side Matrix # GD027A
          GD Productions